What the hell?
Where am I?
I remember being at Egil's place.
Then I left with Asuna.
But I can't remember what happened next.
My clothes.
Am I in a game right now?
Command!
Log out?
Way too realistic to be a 3d
object so this ain't a game.
Am I dreaming?
Wait, that's it.
This is the underworld.
I'm hooked up to the STL.
But that can't be right.
If I'm diving in the STL, my memories
of the real world should be blocked.
and I can still remember hanging
out with Asuna and Xenon.
Kikwoka! Higa!
Anyone, abort the dive!
I think there's something wrong in here!
This is too real for VR.
what was that i don't know why but
it felt so nostalgic and frustrating
Did you do it?
I can't wait.
I'm not a filthy girl yet.
A red man, calm and calm and so on.
I don't know the beginning.
Wow!
I took place by sides.
Baby, we go.
I'm ready to go.
This is the magic of the night.
I'm trying to turn it on.
It's a song that I'm calling you.
To your fingers.
I'm going to start with the.
I'm going to see you
in the end of the day.
Shine your song, my diamond.
I'm going to see you
in the end of the day.
Oh, my God.
Who are you?
Are you from around here?
Is he a tester like me?
Or is he an NPC?
Do you have a name?
Yeah, I got one.
It's Kirito.
Kirito?
I came from the forest over there, but
I'm not sure where I am or anything.
The forest?
Oh, you mean from the south?
Did you walk all the way from Zakaria?
No, I don't think so.
I mean, it's like, I
don't know how I got here.
I can't remember. What?
Then where do you live?
Can you remember the name of the town?
Um, no, everything's a blank.
I woke up and I was in the forest.
I heard the stories, but I never thought
I'd meet a real life lost child of Vecta.
I can't believe it.
Huh?
What's a Vecta?
Wait, isn't that what they're
called where you're from?
When someone disappears from a village,
then suddenly turns up
in a forest or a field.
That's what they're called.
A child of Vecta.
The dark god Vecta likes to prank
humans by snatching them up,
Stealing their memories and plopping
them down somewhere far from home.
Oh.
I guess that must have been
what happened to me then.
His responses are way
too natural for an NPC.
I'll try the direct approach.
Anyway, I'm kind of stuck, so...
I want to leave.
Hmm.
Yes, I'm sure you do.
I think I know how to help you.
The forest is huge and easy
to get lost in, though.
I can show you a path that leads north.
As long as you stick to it, you won't...
Sorry.
I want to log out now.
Log out?
What does that mean?
Damn it.
It's slang, you know?
It's like a faster way of saying I
need to find a place to stay. Really?
I never heard that one before.
Now what?
He could be a tester, but if he is,
his memories are definitely blocked.
My village is called Rulid
and it's beyond those trees,
but we don't get many travelers,
so there's no win.
I think if we go to the church and
explain your situation to Sister Azalea,
she might agree to put you up.
Oh, okay then.
I'll go to your village and talk to her.
Wait a moment.
But you're a stranger in these parts.
I don't think the guards at the gate
are going to let you in so easily.
You know what?
If I go with you and talk to
them, they should understand.
That'd be great if you did.
Thanks a lot.
But I can't go yet.
I have to finish my work first.
And I won't be done
for another four hours.
I don't mind. I can wait.
That is, as long as it's okay with you.
Of course.
Have a seat anywhere you
like, and I'll get to work.
Oh, I haven't told you my name, have I?
No.
My name is Eugeo. How'd you do?
Eugeo?
Sounds familiar.
What's wrong, Sir Kirito?
Nothing.
Oh, and you can just call me Kirito.
Okay.
Nice to make your acquaintance, Kirito.
That's right.
Huh?
You must be hungry.
Oh, thanks a lot.
He's definitely not an NPC.
Still not sure if he's
a test player, though.
Or maybe this isn't VR.
Maybe this is real.
The only good thing about this,
Brett, is it keeps for a long time.
But just to be safe.
Okay, let me try that.
That settles it.
This ain't reality or
a parallel dimension.
It's VR.
Hey, Kirito. What?
Did you forget how to use
the Stacia window too?
No, course not.
You can take your time
eating it if you want.
It still has plenty of life left.
If this were summer, you can bet
it wouldn't keep nearly as long.
Huh?
Holy!
It's not very good, huh?
I get them from the bakery
every morning on my way here,
but so early they only have day-old bread,
and I don't have time to go
back at noon for fresh ones.
That sucks.
Do you have time to make lunch
or have someone else make it?
Well, actually, someone used to bring me
my lunch every day, but that was years ago.
Oh, well.
So why'd they stop?
She was my childhood friend.
She was the same age as me.
When we were little, we
played together all the time.
And after I received my calling, she would
bring me lunch every day without fail.
But then,
because of me, the two of us went to
explore a cave up north, and by accident,
she crossed the boundary
into the Dark Territory,
a place no human is
allowed to enter, ever.
The Taboo Index forbids it.
Taboo Index?
The next day,
an Integrity Knight came to our village,
and he took her to Senator to be executed.
But I still believe she's alive, Kirito.
I know it.
Somewhere in Senator, Alice is alive.
Alice.
I know that name.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to dump all that on you.
I know we just met and all, but
it feels like we're old friends.
That's okay. I don't mind.
So, why don't you go find her?
Go to Senator or wherever.
See if she's there.
Even if I had the fastest
horse in the land,
it would take a week
to get there from here.
Then throw some clothes
and food in a bag and walk.
If I could do that, I would.
But I can't just abandon my calling.
The Taboo Index forbids it.
You know that.
Oh, right. You got a point.
Um, sorry to be nosy, but about how
long ago did all this happen anyway?
It was my 11th summer, six years ago.
Want some water?
Thanks, maybe later.
Well, lunch is over, so I
better get back to work.
I still have to meet my quota for today.
I'll just kick back till you finish then.
By the way, you're calling. What is it?
You'll see.
It's not very exciting.
So, like, you're calling
us to chop down trees?
Yeah.
Officially, my title's
supposed to be woodcutter.
The problem is I haven't
cut a single tree down
in the seven years since
I received my calling.
What?
My job's to work on this tree.
It's called the Giga Cedar.
The villagers call it
something else, though.
The Demon Tree.
They call it that because
it sucks up all of
Terraria's blessings
from the land around it.
Rulid has always wanted to
plant more wheat fields,
but as long as this is here,
nothing good will grow.
The village had that dragon bone
axe sent from the capital and
appointed a woodcutter to work on it
every day till the tree came down.
That's my job.
So, for the past seven years now,
you've been chopping away at it?
After all that time, that's
as far as you got? Hardly.
I'm actually a seventh
generation woodcutter.
That's our calling.
Someone's been chopping away on it.
Every single day.
For 300 years, in fact.
For 300 years?
Hey, Yu-Gi-Oh.
Mind if I take a crack at it? Huh?
I mean, you did give me
half your lunch, didn't you?
So it's only fair I should
pick up half your work.
Oh, I don't know.
I mean, the taboo index doesn't
say I can't have someone help,
even though it is my calling and all.
Try it, but it's much
harder than it looks.
I won't know till I try.
Here goes nothing.
You don't have to laugh that hard.
I'm sorry about that.
You put way too much tension
into your shoulders and hips.
Relax and let the momentum
do the work for you.
That's right.
This is a virtual world.
It's not about my real
ability, but my avatars.
Sword skill?
Smash!
Whoa, that was a nice hit.
Go on, give it another
shot before you forget.
Fifty!
Okay, that's one thousand strikes.
Really?
We did that many today?
Uh-huh.
Five hundred for me and
five hundred for you.
At the thousand I did this morning,
and that's 2,000 strikes total.
That's the daily quota for my calling.
Oh, my God.
You're a natural at this, Kirito.
Thanks to your skill, I
had an easy day today.
I don't know about that.
I bet you would have had it cut down
by now if I wasn't here messing around.
Think so?
Then you need to see something.
It's only gone down by about 50 since
last month that's normal actually
it's a strong tree so what if we
didn't make a lot of progress today in
the end it doesn't really make much
of a difference at all let's go wait
you forgot to lock it what for what
do you mean someone could steal it?
Now who'd do that?
It clearly states in the taboo index
that theft is forbidden, remember?
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Come on, I'll show you my village.
Um, but...
Hey, wait up!
Hey, Eugeo.
Who's your new friend?
Hey, Zink.
This is Kirito.
I think he's a lost child of Vecta.
That true?
You can't remember anything?
Um, no.
Did you forget your calling, too?
Yeah, I guess.
It was probably a lousy calling anyway.
Bet it was as lame as Eugeo's here.
He's got one of the most pointless
callings in all the land.
Now mine, I'm a man-at-arms,
and let me tell...
Swordsman.
That's my calling, man.
I'm a swordsman.
A swordsman?
A scrawny, weak-looking
pipsqueak like you?
You can't even lift a sword.
Go on, then.
Show us your skill.
Let's see how I do with this.
No way.
That was a light effect.
There's sword skills here.
That was amazing.
I didn't know you had skills like that.
Maybe you were a sentinel
in some big city.
I don't know. Maybe.
Zink, will you let Kirito in?
I'd like to show him
around the village now.
I'm tired.
Well, we're here. Finally.
Is this really okay?
I mean, everyone's just going to accept
I'm one of those lost Vecta kids?
Isn't that what you are?
Yeah, I guess so.
Let's talk to the sister
and get you sorted out.
What do you boys want?
Here, I brought you a pillow and a blanket
Prayers begin at 6 o
'clock, breakfast is at 7
I'll come check on you, but please try to
get up on time Do not be late for prayers
You do not want to make
Sister Azalea mad Also,
we have a curfew after
life's out, so mind that
Jesus! Run!
Honestly.
Now then, do you have any questions?
No, I'm good.
Thanks for setting me up.
Well, good night, then.
You know how to put out the lamp, right?
Yeah.
Good night, Selka.
This ain't the real world and as far as I
can tell none of the villagers are NPCs.
But they can't be testers
either there'd have
to be dozens of STLs
for them to log in with.
and I know there aren't that many.
What did Yu-Gi-Oh say?
According to him, more than 300
years have passed in this world.
He spent the last six as a woodcutter
here and remembers his childhood here too.
If that's true, then him and the others...
Hmm?
Oh.
Yu-Gi-Oh and the villagers were
raised here from the start,
but the only way that could happen is
if Wrath copied the souls of babies.
Babies.
Artificial Fluctlights.
It's hard to believe, but
there's no other explanation.
But why would Wrath do that?
And how fast would they have to accelerate
time to get this world to this point?
And what if I'm stuck here
forever and never get back home?
Maybe I can get in touch with Kikuoka
if I can get to a bigger city.
I need money to travel
and right now I got none.
And I don't know enough
about this world yet.
If I had some help, I could get to
Senator and find some answers there.
I am not.
I am not. I am not.
I'm just a star, and I'm just a star,
and I'm just a star.
I don't know.
I'm not going to leave my tears!
I'm not going to hide!
You are not going to look at the face!
I'm not going to hide your eyes!
I'm not going to hide your tears!
If you're next to me, I'm
going to be able to hide!
I'm going to hide my tears!
If I'm going to have a little bit!
Be Alice to you!
Next time, The End Mountains?